YANNI FERNANDA RIBEIRO FRAGA

Location: Praia Grande – SP • Email: yanni_fernanda@hotmail.com • Phone: 55 13 98171-8801
Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/yanni-fraga • Page: yannifraga.com

Summary

Professional with more than 5 years of experience in IT Industry, now focused on Web Development. Challenge seeker, with can-do attitude and a good interpersonal relationship. Works well under pressure, goal-oriented, cares about self-improvement and Company's growth, with main objective to work as a Front-end Developer.

Education

- Development of Web Applications, PUC Minas, Mar 2018 present
- Systems Analysis, Faculdade de Tecnologia de Praia Grande, Feb 2011 Aug 2015
- Certificate in IT, Escola Técnica de Praia Grande ETEC PG, Feb 2008 Jul 2009

Professional Experience

IT Technician/Web Developer, FATEC PG

Aug 2013 – Jan 2017, Feb 2018 – present

- Maintenance and development of the college website, using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SharePoint 2007 and SQL Server.
- Development of the new college website, using HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Bootstrap, jQuery, PHP Laravel and MySQL.
- Creation of images for event posts.
- IT support for students and professors.

Intern, Praia Grande City Hall

Jul 2011 – Jun 2013

Development of educational games using ActionScript 3.0 and Flash CS5.

Skills & Competencies

HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, Angular, PHP

SQL, MySQL

Git, Gulp

PhotoShop, Illustrator

Volunteer Work

❖ Free Geek Vancouver

Jun 2017 – Aug 2018

• Dismantle of small equipment.